[Applause]
if you haven't been living under a rock
you would know that hashtag toto650 is
trending on social media
[Music]
in case you thought crosston was the
go-to tablet for a headache body ache or
fever you need to wake up and smell the
dolo yes that's right in the last two
years dolo has sold far more than crocin
the standard paracetamol tablet it's
dolo 650 which has clocked sales of 567
crores during the pandemic from march
2020 and topped the charts selling more
than 350 pills so much so that it's been
called a favorite snack as india
grapples with the third wave of kovite
19. before the outbreak of kovaid in
2019 india sold around 7.5 crore strips
of dollar pills according to statistics
from research firm equia dolo 650 saw
sales were 28.9 crores in december 2021
up over 60 percent year on year the
tablet's highest sales numbers however
came during april and may 2021 the peak
of the second wave meanwhile nearest
competitor cal paul's december sales
came in at 28 crores if all 350 crore of
the 1.5 centimeter long tablets were
stacked vertically it would be nearly 6
000 times the height of mount everest
the world's highest mountain or 63
thousand times the height of burj
khalifa the world's tallest building
data with equia shows that dolo and
calpol are the key brands driving the
paracetamol segment while dolo 650 is
manufactured by bengaluru based
microlabs calpol is made by gsk
pharmaceuticals other popular brands of
paracetamol include phenyl p250 pacimol
and crocin so what's the secret behind
the success of desi dolo650 why is a hit
with the doctors several reports suggest
dolo is still a medicine that doctors
prescribe unlike crocin moreover doctors
prescribed dolo 650 as it can be given
to people of all ages and has minimal
side effects
some believe dolo 650 has become a brand
whose name is used interchangeably with
paracetamol itself
looks like dolo is set to do what
bislery or xerox did for their
respective products between the third
wave and flu doing the rounds in the
country there's hardly anyone who does
not have at least one person in their
family or friend circle who has a cold
or fever and since paracetamol tablets
are the go-to medicines in both cases
this has given a rise to the consumption
and popularity of dolo 650 giving rise
to memes bringing the usual dose of
humor to the platform
[Music]
it is rare to get information that is
tailor-made for you in this era of
clutter money control india's number one
financial destination has launched money
control pro an ad-free premium service
that offers you subscribers curated
markets data exclusive trading
recommendations and actionable
investment ideas which help you stay on
top of your game
in less than a year money control pro
has become india's fastest growing
subscription service with more than 1.2
lakh active subscribers and growing by
the minute we are grateful to all our
loyal users for making money control pro
an undisputed leader in its category
with several corporate giants
subscribing in large numbers for their
employees subscribe today for a seamless
uninterrupted access to a gamut of
business and financial information
be a pro with money control pro
[Music]